<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Nix on Trip in Tech</title><link>https://tripin.tech/tags/nix/</link><description>Recent content in Nix on Trip in Tech</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://tripin.tech/tags/nix/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Canary Technologies</title><link>https://tripin.tech/portfolio/canary-technologies/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://tripin.tech/portfolio/canary-technologies/</guid><description>Canary Technologies is an industry leader in hospitality management systems.
Strengthening Security and Access Control at Canary Technologies Canary Technologies prioritized enhancing the security of their AWS environment and controlling access to critical resources. I was engaged to implement a robust access control system and ensure comprehensive auditability. My key contributions included:
Implementing Secure Authentication with Google SSO To eliminate the security risks associated with managing individual AWS credentials, I:</description></item><item><title>ArkLight</title><link>https://tripin.tech/portfolio/arklight/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://tripin.tech/portfolio/arklight/</guid><description>ArkLight Security software provides active cyber security protection against the most common threats along with comprehensive cyber insurance coverage.
Building Scalable Infrastructure on Azure and Providing Go Expertise at ArkLight During my time at ArkLight as a contractor, I contributed to two key areas:
Developing Azure Infrastructure with Terraform I was responsible for building and managing scalable infrastructure on Microsoft Azure using Terraform. This involved:
Designing and Implementing Infrastructure as Code: I leveraged Terraform to define and provision various Azure resources, including virtual machines, networking components, and storage solutions.</description></item><item><title>Motive</title><link>https://tripin.tech/portfolio/motive/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://tripin.tech/portfolio/motive/</guid><description>Motive, formerly KeepTruckin, is an industry leader in empowering the people who run the physical economy.
Wael, co-founder of Trip In Tech, led key engineering efforts at Motive for five years (2018-2023). His focus as a Lead Platform Engineer included security, infrastructure, developer productivity, and embedded systems. See some of his notable projects below.
Building a High-Performance Development Ecosystem As a co-founder of Trip In Tech, my passion for optimizing developer workflows stems from my experience leading Motive&amp;rsquo;s developer productivity team.</description></item><item><title>Linnaeus</title><link>https://tripin.tech/portfolio/linnaeus/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://tripin.tech/portfolio/linnaeus/</guid><description>Linnaeus is an open source cybersecurity threat intelligence.
Enhancing Infrastructure Management and Security at Linnaeus Linnaeus relied on AWS to power its infrastructure, and I was brought in to address key challenges related to infrastructure management, security, and access control. My primary focus was on:
Implementing Infrastructure as Code with Terraform Linnaeus needed to gain better control and visibility over its AWS infrastructure. To achieve this, I:
Introduced Terraform for Infrastructure Management: I implemented Terraform to define and manage all infrastructure components as code, enabling version control, collaboration, and automation.</description></item></channel></rss>