<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Contract on Trip in Tech</title><link>https://tripin.tech/categories/contract/</link><description>Recent content in Contract on Trip in Tech</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://tripin.tech/categories/contract/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>ArkLight</title><link>https://tripin.tech/portfolio/arklight/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://tripin.tech/portfolio/arklight/</guid><description>ArkLight Security software provides active cyber security protection against the most common threats along with comprehensive cyber insurance coverage.
Building Scalable Infrastructure on Azure and Providing Go Expertise at ArkLight During Trip In Tech&amp;rsquo;s engagement with ArkLight as a contractor, we contributed to two key areas:
Developing Azure Infrastructure with Terraform We were responsible for building and managing scalable infrastructure on Microsoft Azure using Terraform. This involved:
Designing and Implementing Infrastructure as Code: We leveraged Terraform to define and provision various Azure resources, including virtual machines, networking components, and storage solutions.</description></item><item><title>Linnaeus</title><link>https://tripin.tech/portfolio/linnaeus/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://tripin.tech/portfolio/linnaeus/</guid><description>Linnaeus is an open source cybersecurity threat intelligence.
Enhancing Infrastructure Management and Security at Linnaeus Linnaeus relied on AWS to power its infrastructure, and Trip In Tech was brought in to address key challenges related to infrastructure management, security, and access control. Our primary focus was on:
Implementing Infrastructure as Code with Terraform Linnaeus needed to gain better control and visibility over its AWS infrastructure. To achieve this, we:</description></item></channel></rss>